kirod.com 2019-05-01

# Privacy Policy – Brand That Care – KeepCare

Your privacy is very important to us. Our Privacy Policy spells out Keepcare India’s commitment to respecting the privacy of the members and visitors to our  site https://keepcare.com By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy.

## Information we collect

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our Keepcare India’s Email Club, respond to a survey, give a review or fill out a form. However, should you not wish to purchase a product you may visit our site anonymously.

we collect data that is required for communication and to deliver purchased products by visitors on https://keepcare.com . We only collect phone number and address of our client which is solely provide by the Visitors Itself.  Keepcare.com’s visitors agree with terms and condition that permit to use data provided by visitors.

## Other information we might collect

Keepcare India and our third party partners, for example advertisers and content providers, may also collect statistical information while you use our site. Statistical information that we gather may include where a user is and on the Internet (e.g. the URL that they last came from, the computer’s IP address and the domain types like .com etc. that the user uses), browser type, which language content is being viewed in, the country and telephone area code where the computer is located, the pages of our website that were viewed during the visit, the advertisements that were clicked on and any search terms that were entered on our website. We do not use this information to identify you personally and we may collect it even if you are not a registered user.

## How information is used

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * -To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * -To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * -To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * -To process transactions (Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * -To communicate with you (About our brand, products, events or other promotional purposes, if you have opted to receive such communications.The email address you provide for order processing, will be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.)
  * -To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * -To support our marketing and research purposes

## Disclosure of Information

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. Keepcare India uses other reputed and trusted companies to perform functions on our behalf in relation to the purposes included in this Privacy Policy. Such functions include credit/debit card validation and authorization, web hosting, data analysis, order fulfillment and mailings. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. However, if required by the law, we may need provide all information to enforce our site policies or to protect the rights, property or safety of others as well as our own.

## Security

Keepcare India takes the privacy of its customers very seriously and we are committed to protecting the security of your data, both on and off line.

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and is collected, processed and encrypted directly into 2Checkout’s Payment gateway database server only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

For your protection, Keepcare India does not store or provide access to credit card information, which is why you will be required to re-enter your credit card and expiration date with every online credit card transaction. For security reasons, we strongly recommend that you do not send credit card numbers by standard email and only use the secure facility provided on our website.

You represent and warrant that you have the legal right to use any credit card(s) utilized in connection with any transaction

## Cookies

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow it to) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly.

## Third Party Links

Please be aware that, when you are on the site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. These other sites may transmit their own “cookies” to visitors, collect data or solicit personal information. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any information that may be collected there.

## Your reviews / product testimonials

You can choose to add product reviews and share your experience with our products. This is optional rather than obligatory part of being a registered user on keepcare.com our product reviews may be used in our marketing and promotional material and/or any of our partner companies who we work with to serve customers. You have the right to have your review removed at any time, in this event you should send our customer service team your request by email on support@keepcare.com

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may update this privacy statement. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## Phone Number And Address Details

Our Visitors phone number is only used for Promotional and Transnational alerts only. Address details are required for Shipping purpose only. We Don’t Distribute or Sell personal data of our clients, site’s visitor.
